colormerad.com 2015-06-11

# Privacy Policy - Color Me Rad 5K Run

##### Our Commitment to Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

##### What information do we collect?

We collect information when you fill out your race registration, including your name, email, address, phone number, date of birth and payment details.

We also use various Google Analytics features in order to improve the customer experience on our website and to improve its efficacy. These features include demographics and interests, Adwords linking, and remarketing.

You can choose to opt-out of the Google Analytics Advertising Features we use through Google Ad Settings, Ad Settings for mobile apps, or any other available means (such as the National Advertising Initiative’s (NAI) consumer opt-out).

##### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information collected may be used to improve our website, improve customer service, to process transactions, to send periodic emails with information about The Color Me Rad race, to administer a contest, survey, promotion of other racing events or other site features. All credit card information will be used only to process the registration for the current registration purchased and will only be shared with those affiliated with processing the transaction and is not stored by Color Me Rad.

We may also release information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. Non-personally identifiable information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Your email address will never be sold to outside affiliates.

##### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information and all measures will be taken to protect this information.

##### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

##### Consent

By using our site and submitting your registration, you hereby consent to the online privacy policy, as stated.

By submitting, posting or displaying any content, pictures and other materials on our Facebook page, you grant to us a worldwide, non-exclusive, royalty-free license (with the right to sublicense) to use, copy, reproduce, process, adapt, modify, publish, transmit, display and distribute such content, pictures or other materials in any and all media, advertising, marketing or other distribution methods whether now known or later developed.

##### Changes to Privacy Policy

Any changes made to this privacy policy will be noted on this page.

This policy was last modified on 06/02/2014.

##### Contact

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information listed below:

Color Me Rad  
(202) 656-7723  
info@colormerad.com
